irazoo.com 2007-12-11

# Search Engine, Meta search engine, Best search engine

| 

iRazoo is committed to protecting the privacy of its Users. iRazoo will never share any of your personal information without your permission. Anonymity is of significant value to the site (iRazoo.com) and its Users. This site will take all reasonable precautions to protect the anonymity of its Users (registered or not) with respect to all transactions, query requests, and results. These precautions extend to the design of the site, the use of all information, and all other actions, which are under the control of the site. All Users shall respect and support this goal of maintaining User privacy and anonymity. Use of the site, or any information gained from the use of the site in an attempt to compromise the anonymity of any other User is strictly forbidden. Please read below for more information about our privacy policy.

**Information we collect**  
If you choose to register, iRazoo asks for your contact information (e.g. name, address, city, state). The User does not have to provide any personal information to use iRazoo. However, if you choose to withhold requested information, you will not be registered and you will not earn Razoo Points, which can be redeemed for gift certificates and other items from our Merchant Partners. In addition, we may not be able to provide you with some of the other services which are dependent upon the collection of such information, such as your RazooWallet and your Wish List. While using our site, iRazoo automatically tracks certain information about you. This information includes the URL you just came from (whether this URL is from our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is from our site or not), what browser you are using, and your IP address. This information is collected to analyze trends, track user movement and use patterns, track the total number of unique Users to the site, gather broad demographic information otherwise required to receive goods and services, information to be received from User surveys conducted from time to time, and information required to enter into and administer the site. iRazoo may require additional information from its Users such as: information provided to receive goods and services, information received from user surveys, and information collected from entries into contests or promotions that are sponsored from time to time by iRazoo or its Merchant Partners.

**Information Security**  
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, iRazoo cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

**Consent to our Privacy Policy**  
By using iRazoo, you agree to the above uses of your personal information. If at any time this policy changes, those changes will be posted to this page so that you are aware of our intent to better protect your privacy. Your use of iRazoo constitutes your agreement with the terms of iRazoo's privacy policy and your continued use of iRazoo constitutes your agreement to any changes that may be made to such terms.

**Opting out of emails**  
You have the choice of whether or not to disclose personally identifiable information. However, you must provide some personally identifiable information in order to become a registered iRazoo User. You can choose at anytime to opt out of receiving emails from iRazoo or from having your personally identifiable information shared with certain companies. If you elect to "opt out" we will not share your personal information with third parties or send you emails. However, iRazoo may continue to use your personal information for internal purposes, promotions, to enhance your User experience or as necessary to administer the site or comply with applicable law.

**Special Promotions**  
iRazoo may disclose your personal information to Merchant Partners or sponsors of promotions available through iRazoo. Special sponsor promotions may often involve a request for additional information. By submitting this additional information, you give iRazoo permission to transfer this information to the sponsor so they may fulfill your request or administer the promotion.

**Compliance with the Law**  
iRazoo may also disclose your information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) iRazoo's rights or property, other iRazoo users or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. In addition, iRazoo may disclose or access account information for administrative and other purposes that we believe are necessary to develop, maintain and improve our products and services.

**Additional Information**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact us at:

iRazoo.com  
5644 Westheimer, #407  
Houston, Texas, 77056  
or feedback@iRAZOO.com

This privacy policy was last updated on January 6th, 2007
